A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Healthy Steps for Young Children Program, SG 2, Series 6 FA498
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Healthy Steps for Young Children Program, SG 2, Series 6
1985-2007
1991-2004
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA498
72.2 Cubic Feet 190 document boxes.
185 document boxes.
Scope and Contents
Contains documentation of the Healthy Steps for Young Children program, from its inception through the mid-2000s, including planning documents, correspondence, reports, program and site evaluations, and related grant records.
Arrangement
Sub-Series: 1. Chronologocial Files; 2. Evaluations; 3. General Files; 4. Grants; 5. Meetings; 6. Working Papers; 7. Program Reports; 8. Reports and Surveys; 9. Publications; and 10. Special Formats.
Within each subseries file arrangements are in chronlogical, reverse chronological and/or Alphabetical order.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
- Chronological Files, 1995-2007; 1
  - Year 1 - Volume 1, 1995 January-March (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Year 1 - Volume 1, 1995 April-July (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Year 1 - Volume II, 1995 August (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Year 1 - Volume II, 1995 September-October (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Year 1 - Volume III, 1995 October-November (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Year 2 - Volume I, 1995 December 1-31 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Year 2 - Volume I, 1996 January 1-15 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Year 2 - Volume I, 1996 January 16-31 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Year 2 - Volume II, 1996 January 16-29 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Year 2 - Volume III, 1996 February 1-28 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Year 2 - Volume III, 1996 March 1-15 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Year 2 - Volume III, 1996 March 16-31 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Year 2 - Volume IV, 1996 April 1-15 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Year 2 - Volume V, 1996 April 16-30 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Year 2 - Volume V, 1996 May 1-15 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Year 2 - Volume VI, 1996 May 16-30 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Year 2 - Volume VI, 1996 June 1-15 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Year 2 - Volume VII, 1996 June 16-31 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Year 2 - Volume VII, 1996 July 1-15 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Year 2 - Volume VIII, 1996 July 16-31 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Year 2 - Volume VIII, 1996 August 1-31 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Year 2 - Volume IX, 1996 September 1-15 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Year 2 - Volume IX, 1996 September 16-31 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Year 2 - Volume X, 1996 October 1-15 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Year 2 - Volume X, 1996 October 16-31 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Year 2 - Volume XI, 1996 November (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Year 2 - Volume XI, 1996 December (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Year 3 - Volume I, 1997 January 1-15 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Year 3 - Volume I, 1997 January 16-31 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Year 3 - Volume II, 1997 February (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Year 3 - Volume II, 1997 March 1-15 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Year 3 - Volume III, 1997 March 16 - April 15 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Year 3 - Volume III, 1997 April - May 15 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Year 3 - Volume IV, 1997 May - June (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Year 3 - Volume IV, 1997 July - Aug. 15 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Year 3 - Volume V, 1997 August (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Year 3 - Volume V, 1997 September (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Year 3 - Volume V, 1997 October 1-16 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Year 3 - Volume VI, 1997 October 16-31 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Year 3 - Volume VI, 1997 November (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Year 3 - Volume VI, 1997 December (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Year 4 - Volume I, 1998 January (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Year 4 - Volume I, 1998 February (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Year 4 - Volume I, 1998 March 1-15 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Year 4 - Volume II, 1998 March 16-31 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Year 4 - Volume II, 1998 April (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Year 4 - Volume II, 1998 May 1-15 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Year 4 - Volume III, 1998 May-June (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Year 4 - Volume III, 1998 July 1-22 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Year 4 - Volume III, 1998 July 23-31 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Year 4 - Volume IV, 1998 August 1-6 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Year 4 - Volume IV, 1998 August 6-31 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Year 4 - Volume V, 1998 September (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Year 4 - Volume V, 1998 October 1-15 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Year 4 - Volume VI, 1998 October 16-31 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Year 4 - Volume VI, 1998 November 1-27 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Year 4 - Volume VII, 1998 November 29-30 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Year 4 - Volume VII, 1998 December 1-31 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Year 5 - Volume I, 1999 January (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Year 5 - Volume I, 1999 February (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Year 5 - Volume II, 1999 March 1-15 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Year 5 - Volume II, 1999 March 16-31 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Year 5 - Volume III, 1999 April 1-15 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Year 5 - Volume III, 1999 April 16 - May 15 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Year 5 - Volume IV, 1999 May 16-31 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Year 5 - Volume IV, 1999 June 1-15 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Year 5 - Volume IV, 1999 June 16-30 (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Year 5 - Volume V, 1999 July (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - Year 5 - Volume V, 1999 August 1-13 (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - Year 5 - Volume V, 1999 August 13-31 (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - Year 5 - Volume VI, 1999 September-October (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Year 5 - Volume VI, 1999 November (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - Year 5 - Volume VII, 1999 December-2000 January (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - Year 6 - Volume I, 2000 January-February (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - Year 6 - Volume I, 2000 February 7-10 (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - Year 6 - Volume I, 2000 February-March 15 (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - Year 6 - Volume II, 2000 March 16-29 (Box 22, Folder 77)
  - Year 6 - Volume II, 2000 March 29-31 (Box 22, Folder 78)
  - Year 6 - Volume II, 2000 April 1-15 (Box 22, Folder 79)
  - Year 6 - Volume III, 2000 April-May (Box 22, Folder 80)
  - Year 6 - Volume III, 2000 May-June (Box 22, Folder 81)
  - Year 6 - Volume III, 2000 June 7-29 (Box 23, Folder 82)
  - Year 6 - Volume IV, 2000 July (Box 23, Folder 83)
  - Year 6 - Volume IV, 2000 August 1-7 (Box 23, Folder 84)
  - Year 6 - Volume IV, 2000 August 7-14 (Box 23, Folder 85)
  - Year 6 - Volume V, 2000 August 15-31 (Box 23, Folder 86)
  - Year 6 - Volume V, 2000 September 1-15 (Box 24, Folder 87)
  - Year 6 - Volume V, 2000 September 15-30 (Box 24, Folder 88)
  - Year 6 - Volume VI, 2000 October 1-16 (Box 24, Folder 89)
  - Year 6 - Volume VI, 2000 October 16-26 (Box 24, Folder 90)
  - Year 6 - Volume VI, 2000 October 26-30 (Box 24, Folder 91)
  - Year 6 - Volume VII, 2000 November 1-15 (Box 25, Folder 92)
  - Year 6 - Volume VII, 2000 November 16-29 (Box 25, Folder 93)
  - Year 6 - Volume VIII, 2000 November 30 (Box 25, Folder 94)
  - Year 6 - Volume IX, 2000 December 1-31 (Box 25, Folder 95)
  - Year 6 - Volume IX, 20001 January 1-15 (Box 26, Folder 96)
  - Year 7 - Volume I, 2001 January 16-31 (Box 26, Folder 97)
  - Year 7 - Volume I, 2001 February 1-15 (Box 26, Folder 98)
  - Year 7 - Volume I, 2001 February 16-28 (Box 26, Folder 99)
  - Year 7 - Volume II, 2001 March 1-15 (Box 26, Folder 100)
  - Year 7 - Volume II, 2001 March (Box 26, Folder 101)
  - Year 7 - Volume II, 2001 March 16-30 (Box 27, Folder 102)
  - Year 7 - Volume III, 2001 April 1-15 (Box 27, Folder 103)
  - Year 7 - Volume III, 2001 April 16-27 (Box 27, Folder 104)
  - Year 7 - Volume III, 2000 April 27-30 (Box 27, Folder 105)
  - Year 7 - Volume IV, 2001 May 1-10 (Box 27, Folder 106)
  - Year 7 - Volume IV, 2001 May 10-31 (Box 28, Folder 107)
  - Year 7 - Volume V, 2001 June 1 (Box 28, Folder 108)
  - Year 7 - Volume V, 2001 June 1-14 (Box 28, Folder 109)
  - Year 7 - Volume V, 2001 June 14-27 (Box 28, Folder 110)
  - Year 7 - Volume VI, 2001 June 28 (Box 29, Folder 112)
  - Year 7 - Volume VI, 2001 July 1 (Box 28, Folder 111)
  - Year 7 - Volume VI, 2001 July 2-25 (Box 29, Folder 113)
  - Year 7 - Volume VII, 2001 July 26-30 (Box 29, Folder 114)
  - Year 7 - Volume VII, 2001 August (Box 29, Folder 115)
  - Year 7 - Volume VII, 2001 September (Box 29, Folder 116)
  - Year 7 - Volume VIII, 2001 October (Box 29, Folder 117)
  - Year 7 - Volume VIII, 2001 November 1-15 (Box 30, Folder 118)
  - Year 7 - Volume IX, 2001 November 16-30 (Box 30, Folder 119)
  - Year 7 - Volume IX, 2001 December 1-31 (Box 30, Folder 120)
  - Year 8 - Volume I, 2002 January (Box 30, Folder 121)
  - Year 8 - Volume I, 2002 February-March 8 (Box 30, Folder 122)
  - Year 8 - Volume II, 2002 March 11-April 3 (Box 31, Folder 123)
  - Year 8 - Volume II, 2002 April 3-25 (Box 31, Folder 124)
  - Year 8 - Volume II, 2002 April 25-30 (Box 31, Folder 125)
  - Year 8 - Volume III, 2002 May 1-17 (Box 32, Folder 128)
  - Year 8 - Volume III, 2002 May 17-31 (Box 32, Folder 129)
  - Year 8 - Volume III, 2002 June 1-28 (Box 32, Folder 130)
  - Year 8 - Volume IV, 2002 July 1-15 (Box 32, Folder 131)
  - Year 8 - Volume IV, 2002 July 16-31 (Box 32, Folder 132)
  - Year 8 - Volume IV, 2002 July 31 (Box 33, Folder 133)
  - Year 8 - Volume V, 2002 August-September 15 (Box 31, Folder 126)
  - Year 8 - Volume V, 2002 September 16-October 31 (Box 31, Folder 127)
  - Year 8 - Volume VI, 2002 November 1-21 (Box 33, Folder 134)
  - Year 8 - Volume VI, 2002 November 22-30 (Box 33, Folder 135)
  - Year 9 - Volume I, 2002 December (Box 33, Folder 136)
  - Year 9 - Volume I, 2003 January 1-15 (Box 33, Folder 137)
  - Year 9 - Volume I, 2003 January 16-31 (Box 34, Folder 138)
  - Year 9 - Volume II, 2003 February-March 6 (Box 34, Folder 139)
  - Year 9 - Volume II, 2003 March 6-20 (Box 34, Folder 140)
  - Year 9 - Volume II, 2003 March 21-31 (Box 34, Folder 141)
  - Year 9 - Volume III, 2003 April 1-21 (Box 34, Folder 142)
  - Year 9 - Volume III, 2003 April-May 6 (Box 35, Folder 143)
  - Year 9 - Volume III, 2003 May 6-15 (Box 35, Folder 144)
  - Year 9 - Volume IV, 2003 May 16-June 16 (Box 35, Folder 145)
  - Year 9 - Volume IV, 2003 June 16-July 19 (Box 35, Folder 146)
  - Year 9 - Volume IV, 2003 July 30-31 (Box 35, Folder 147)
  - Year 9 - Volume V, 2003 August-September 15 (Box 36, Folder 148)
  - Year 9 - Volume V, 2003 September 16-30 (Box 36, Folder 149)
  - Year 9 - Volume V, 2003 October 1-15 (Box 36, Folder 150)
  - Year 9 - Volume VI, 2003 October 16 -31 (Box 36, Folder 151)
  - Year 9 - Volume VI, 2003 November 1-30 (Box 36, Folder 152)
  - Year 9 - Volume VII, 2003 December 1-10 (Box 37, Folder 153)
  - Year 9 - Volume VII, 2003 December 10-15 (Box 37, Folder 154)
  - Year 10 - Volume I, 2003 December 16-30 (Box 37, Folder 155)
  - Year 10 - Volume I, 2004 January 1-15 (Box 37, Folder 156)
  - Year 10 - Volume II, 2004 January 16- February (Box 38, Folder 157)
  - Year 10 - Volume II, 2004 February 3-15 (Box 38, Folder 158)
  - Year 10 - Volume III, 2004 February 16-28 (Box 38, Folder 159)
  - Year 10 - Volume III, 2004 March 1-31 (Box 38, Folder 160)
  - Year 10 - Volume IV, 2004 April 1-30 (Box 39, Folder 161)
  - Year 10 - Volume IV, 2004 May 1-31 (Box 39, Folder 162)
  - Year 10 - Volume IV, 2004 June 1-14 (Box 39, Folder 163)
  - Year 10 - Volume V, 2004 June 15-July 30 (Box 39, Folder 164)
  - Year 10 - Volume V, 2004 August-September (Box 39, Folder 165)
  - Year 10 - Volume V, 2004 October 1-31 (Box 39, Folder 166)
  - Year 11 - Volume I, 2004 November-December (Box 40, Folder 167)
  - Year 11 - Volume I, 2005 January-February (Box 40, Folder 168)
  - Year 11 - Volume II, 2005 March 1-31 (Box 40, Folder 169)
  - Year 11 - Volume II, 2005 April-May (Box 40, Folder 170)
  - Year 11 - Volume II, 2005 June 1-30 (Box 40, Folder 171)
  - Year 11 - Volume III, 2005 August-October (Box 41, Folder 172)
  - Year 11 - Volume III, 2005 July 1-31 (Box 41, Folder 173)
  - Year 12 - Volume I, 2006 February (Box 41, Folder 174)
  - Year 12 - Volume I, 2006 March (Box 41, Folder 175)
  - Year 12 - Volume I, 2006 April-May (Box 41, Folder 176)
  - Year 12 - Volume II, 2006 June-July (Box 41, Folder 177)
  - Year 12 - Volume II, 2006 August-December (Box 42, Folder 178)
  - Year 12 - Volume III, 2007 January-December (Box 42, Folder 179)
- Evaluations, 1966-2006; 2
  Arrangement
  Arranged in three subseries: 1. Evaluations - General; 2. Sites; 3. New Practices.
  - Evaluations - General, 1995-2000; 1
    - Evaluation Pilot Sites & Meeting, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 180)
    - Evaluation Measures, 1995-1996 (Box 42, Folder 181)
    - Evaluation Manual, 1996 Sept. 5 (Box 42, Folder 182)
    - Evaluation Design - Final, 1996 Dec. 30 (Box 42, Folder 183)
    - Evaluation Manual - 12 Month Provider Survey - Key Informant Interviews & KAP Questionnaries - Westminster Medical Facility, Colorado, 2000 Jan. 19 (Box 42, Folder 184)
    - Program Evaluation - Medical Record Abstraction Manual, 2000 Jan. (Box 42, Folder 185)
  - Sites, 1966-2005; 2
    Loosely arranged alphabetically by state.
    - Implementation Plan - Site Visits - Agreement With Sites and Draft Letter of Agreement, 1995-1996 (Box 43, Folder 186)
    - Monitoring Site Visits Reports, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 187)
    - Operations Manual for Evaluation Sites, 1997 Feb. (Box 43, Folder 188)
    - Site Quality Rating Measures - Healthy Families America, 1997-1998 (Box 43, Folder 189)
    - Site Quality Rating Measures - ICF Draft - Instruments 1 & 2, 1997-1998 (Box 43, Folder 190)
    - Site Quality Rating Measures - Summaries, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 191)
    - Sites - Question & Answer Sheet, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 192)
    - Sites D-N, 1994-1998 (Box 43, Folder 193)
    - Sites P-V, 1996-2000 (Box 44, Folder 194)
    - Sites - UCLA - Los Angles, CA, 1995-1996 (Box 44, Folder 195)
    - Sites - San Mateo, CA. - Peninsula Community Foundations, 1995-1996 (Box 44, Folder 196)
    - Sites - Kaiser, San Diego, CA., 1996-1997 (Box 44, Folder 197)
    - Site Reference Binder - San Diego, CA. Evaluation, 1997-2000 (Box 44, Folder 198)
    - Sites - Denver. Co.- Colorado Trust, 1997-1999 (Box 44, Folder 199)
    - Site Visit II - Western Colorado Pediatric Associates, Colorado Trust 1996, 1996-1999 (Box 44, Folder 200)
    - Grand Junction, Colorado - Correspondence - Budget, Site Visit, & Agreements, Vol I, 1996-2000 (Box 45, Folder 201)
    - Grand Junction, Colorado - Correspondence - Directory, Site Selection, & Planning Vol.1, 1996-1997 (Box 45, Folder 202)
    - Grand Junction, Colorado - Correspondence - Extension/Sustainability Vol. II, 1998-2005 (Box 45, Folder 203)
    - Grand Junction, Colorado - Correspondence - General Vol. II, 1996-2005 (Box 45, Folder 204)
    - Grand Junction, Colorado - Miscellaneous Vol. II, 1997-1999 (Box 45, Folder 205)
    - Grand Junction, Colorado - Site Reference Binder - Evaluation, 1996-2000 (Box 46, Folder 206)
    - Chicago, IL - Correspondence - Budget, Site Visit, & Check List, Vol. I, 1996-2000 (Box 46, Folder 207)
    - Chicago, IL - Correspondence - Vol. II, 1996-1999 (Box 46, Folder 208)
    - Chicago, IL - Correspondence - Vol. II, 2002-2003 (Box 47, Folder 209)
    - Chicago, IL - Correspondence - Vol. III, 1998-2004 (Box 47, Folder 210)
    - Chicago, IL - Correspondence - Vol. III, 2004-2005 (Box 47, Folder 211)
    - Chicago, IL - Correspondence - Vol. IV, 2005-2006 (Box 47, Folder 212)
    - Affiliated Sites - Chicago, IL - ICF Incorporated, 1996 March-April (Box 48, Folder 213)
    - Affiliated Sites - Chicago, IL - ICF Incorporated, 1996-1997 (Box 48, Folder 214)
    - Affiliated Sites - Chicago, IL - ICF Incorporated, 1997-1998 (Box 48, Folder 215)
    - Site Reference, Chicago, IL - Bethany Hospital - Affiliate, 1997-2001 (Box 48, Folder 216)
    - Site Reference, Chicago, IL - Evaluation, 1996-2000 (Box 48, Folder 217)
    - Site Reference, Chicago, IL - Ravenswood Hospital - Affiliate, 1997-2001 (Box 48, Folder 218)
    - Kansas Health Foundation - Wichita, KS., 1996-1999 (Box 49, Folder 219)
    - Site Reference Binder - Garden City, Kansas - Affiliate, 1997-2001 (Box 49, Folder 220)
    - Iowa City, IA - University of Iowa Hospitals and Clinics, 1966-1999 (Box 49, Folder 221)
    - Iowa City, IA - Site Reference Binder - Evaluation, 1996-2001 (Box 49, Folder 222)
    - Boston, MA - Board of Directors Meeting and Site Visit - Agenda, 1998 July 8-10 (Box 49, Folder 223)
    - Boston, MA - Board of Directors Site visit - Briefing Material, 1998 July 8-10 (Box 49, Folder 224)
    - Boston, MA - Boston Foundation, 1996-1999 (Box 50, Folder 225)
    - Boston, MA - Correspondence - Agreement, Directory, Site Selections and Planning Vol. I, 1996-1997 (Box 50, Folder 226)
    - Boston, MA - Correspondence - Grant, Budget, Site Visit and Check List Vol. 1, 1997-1999 (Box 50, Folder 227)
    - Boston, MA - Correspondence - Extension Sustainability Vol. II, 1998-2005 (Box 50, Folder 228)
    - Boston, MA - Correspondence - General Vol. II, 1995-2005 (Box 50, Folder 229)
    - Site Reference Binder - Evaluation, 1996-2000 (Box 51, Folder 230)
    - Site Visit Information - Revere, MA, 1996-1997 (Box 51, Folder 231)
    - Detroit, MI - Henry Ford Health System, 1996-1999 (Box 51, Folder 232)
    - Detroit, MI - Site Reference Binder - Evaluation, 1996-2001 (Box 51, Folder 233)
    - Detroit, MI - Site Visit Information, 1996-1997 (Box 51, Folder 234)
    - Kansas City, MO - KC Humana - Correspondence - Directory, Site Selection, & Planning, 1996-1997 (Box 51, Folder 235)
    - Kansas City, MO - KC Humana - Correspondence - MVS Report, Check List, Budget & Agreement, 1996-2000 (Box 52, Folder 236)
    - Kansas City, MO - KC Humana - Correspondence - General, 1995-2004 (Box 52, Folder 237)
    - KU Medwest - Correspondence - Site Selection and Planning Vol. I, 1995-1997 (Box 52, Folder 238)
    - KU Medwest - Correspondence - Site Visit, Check List, Agreement, and Directory Vol. I, 1996-1997 (Box 52, Folder 239)
    - KU Medwest - Correspondence - Grant and Budget Vol. I, 1996-2000 (Box 53, Folder 240)
    - KU Medwest - Correspondence - Extensions/Sustainability, Vol. II, 1998-2004 (Box 53, Folder 241)
    - KU Medwest - Correspondence - General Vol. II, 1996-2005 (Box 53, Folder 242)
    - KU Medwest - Site Visit, 1999 Sept. 15 (Box 53, Folder 243)
    - Kansas City, MO - Greater Kansas City Community Foundation, 1995-1996 (Box 54, Folder 244)
    - Kansas City, MO - Prime Health, 1996-1999 (Box 54, Folder 245)
    - Missouri-Kansas City - BlueCross BlueShield, 1997-1998 (Box 54, Folder 246)
    - Site Reference, Kansas City, MO - Blue Cross Blue Shield - Evaluation, 1996-2000 (Box 54, Folder 247)
    - Site Reference, Kansas City, MO - Humana Health Care Plans - Evaluation, 1996-2000 (Box 54, Folder 248)
    - New York, N.Y., 1969-1999 (Box 54, Folder 249)
    - Site Reference Binder - Evaluation, 1997-1999 (Box 55, Folder 250)
    - Rochester, N.Y., 1995-1996 (Box 55, Folder 251)
    - Chapel Hill, NC - Correspondence - General Vol. II, 1995-1999 (Box 55, Folder 254)
    - Chapel Hill, NC - Correspondence - General, Vol. II, 1999-2005 (Box 56, Folder 255)
    - Sites - Chapel Hill, N.C., 1995-1999 (Box 56, Folder 257)
    - Chapel Hill, NC - Site Reference - Evaluation, 1996-2001 (Box 56, Folder 258)
    - Sites - Duke Endowment - Charlotte, N.C., 1995-1997 (Box 56, Folder 259)
    - Site Visit Information - Charlotte, N.C., 1996-1998 (Box 56, Folder 260)
    - Charlotte, NC - Site Reference - Affiliate, 1996-2001 (Box 57, Folder 261)
    - Sites - Lumberton, N. C., 1998 (Box 57, Folder 262)
    - Lumberton, NC - Site Reference - Lumberton Children's Clinc, 1996-2000 (Box 57, Folder 263)
    - Allentown, PA - Correspondence - Agreements, Directory, Site Selection & Planning, Vol. I, 1996, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 264)
    - Allentown, PA - Correspondence - Budget, Site Visit, Monitoring & Checklist Vol. I, 1997-2000 (Box 57, Folder 265)
    - Allentown, PA - Correspondence - General Vol. II, 1995-1996 (Box 57, Folder 266)
    - Allentown, PA - Correspondence - General Vol. II, 1996-2006 (Box 58, Folder 267)
    - Allentown, PA - Correspondence - Ext./Sustain Vol. II, 1998-2003 (Box 58, Folder 268)
    - Sites - Allentown, PA., 1995-1996 (Box 58, Folder 269)
    - Site - Allentown, PA., 1996-1998 (Box 58, Folder 270)
    - Site Reference - Allentown, PA. Pilot Site, 1996-2001 (Box 58, Folder 271)
    - Site Reference - Pittsburgh, PA. - Evaluation, 1996-2001 (Box 59, Folder 272)
    - Florence, South Carolina - Correspondence - Site Visit, Budget, Checklist, Agreement, Site Selection, Planning, Vol. I, 1996-2000 (Box 59, Folder 273)
    - Florence, South Carolina - Correspondence - Extension/Sustainability Vol. II, 1995-2004 (Box 59, Folder 274)
    - Florence, South Carolina - Miscellaneous, 1988-1996 (Box 60, Folder 275)
    - Florence, SC - Site Reference Binder - Evaluation, 1996-2000 (Box 60, Folder 276)
    - Amarillo, TX - Site Visit Information, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 277)
    - Amarillo, TX - Correspondence - Site and Planning Vol. I, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 278)
    - Amarillo, TX - Correspondence - Grant, Budget, Checklist, Agreement & Directory Vol. I, 1997-2000 (Box 60, Folder 279)
    - Amarillo, TX - Correspondence - Extension/Sustainability & General Correspondence Vol. II, 1995-2006 (Box 61, Folder 280)
    - Amarillo, TX - Site Reference - Evaluation, 1996-2000 (Box 61, Folder 281)
    - Site Reference - Houston, TX - Affiliate, 1995-2000 (Box 61, Folder 282)
    - Site Reference Binder - Richmond, TX - Evaluation, 1996-2001 (Box 61, Folder 283)
    - Site Visit Information - San Antonio, TX., 1998 (Box 61, Folder 284)
    - Site Reference Binder - San Antonio, TX Affiliate, 1996-2000 (Box 62, Folder 285)
    - Site Reference Binder - Group Health Cooperative of Puget Sound - Seattle, WA., 1996-1999 (Box 62, Folder 286)
  - New Practices, 2003-2006; 3
    Loosely arranged by state.
    - Site Updates - Original/New Practices, 2003 (Box 62, Folder 287)
    - A - I, 2000-2007 (Box 62, Folder 288)
    - I - L, 2000-2007 (Box 62, Folder 289)
    - MA - MI, 2000-2006; 2001-2006 (Box 63, Folder 290)
    - MO -MT, 2001-2006 (Box 63, Folder 291)
    - N - O, 1999-2007 (Box 63, Folder 292)
    - O - S, 2000-2007 (Box 63, Folder 293)
    - T, 1999-2006 (Box 64, Folder 294)
    - U - W, 2000-2006 (Box 64, Folder 295)
    - Arizona, 2003-2007 (Box 64, Folder 296)
    - Phoenix, AZ, 2000-2001 (Box 64, Folder 297)
    - Phoenix, AZ, 2002-2003 (Box 64, Folder 298)
    - Phoenix, AZ, 2004-2006 (Box 65, Folder 299)
    - Phoenix, AZ, 2005-2006 (Box 65, Folder 300)
    - California - A - I, 2000-2005 (Box 65, Folder 301)
    - California - L - M, 2000-2007 (Box 65, Folder 302)
    - California - O - V, 2002-2006 (Box 65, Folder 303)
    - Fresno, CA., 2003-2004 (Box 66, Folder 304)
    - Fresno, CA., 2005-2007 (Box 66, Folder 305)
    - Colorado - Boulder, Burlington & Children's Hospital, Denver, 2004-2006 (Box 66, Folder 306)
    - Denver, CO, 2001 (Box 66, Folder 307)
    - Colorado - L - M, 2001-2004 (Box 66, Folder 308)
    - Florida - D - F, 2005-2006 (Box 66, Folder 309)
    - Florida - M - T, 2002-2006 (Box 67, Folder 310)
    - Chicago, IL - C - F, 2001-2005 (Box 67, Folder 311)
    - Chicago, IL - I, 2001-2006 (Box 67, Folder 312)
    - Chicago, IL - L - W, 2001-2007 (Box 67, Folder 313)
    - Chicago, IL - General, 2006 (Box 67, Folder 314)
    - Missouri Kansas Swope, 2000-2006 (Box 67, Folder 315)
    - Missouri Kansas Swope, 2006-2007 (Box 68, Folder 316)
    - Rochester, New York, 1996-2000 (Box 68, Folder 317)
    - Rochester, New York, 2000-2001 (Box 68, Folder 318)
    - Rochester, NY, 2001-2005 (Box 68, Folder 319)
    - North Carolina, 2001-2005 (Box 68, Folder 320)
- General Files, 1989-2005; 3